Philip Ashton Rollins Collection, 1887-1950 (bulk 1900-1930 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 6: Photographs and Films, 1922; 5 boxes
  - 2 reel-to-reel films (3.75") in boxes: titled "Sam Thompson's birthday, All Leaving Round Up" and untitled, dates not examined; portion of 1 box
  - 1 reel-to-reel film (3"): titled "Junius Morgan at Ivy Club June 1929", dates not examined; portion of 1 box
  - "Photographs Taken during the Princeton Scientific Expedition of 1889", undated; 1 box (Box 23)
    Photograph album presented to the Library by Rollins, Class of 1889. The photographs are captioned; participants include Prof. W. B. Scott, H. M. Alexander (Class of 1890), James Boyd (Class of 1886), Furman Kneeland (Class of 1889), and Arthur M. Miller (Class of 1884). Numerous camp scenes and daily activities.
  - Portraits of Rollins, circa 1870-1905; AM 2016-51; 1 folder (Folder 1)
  - Portraits of Rollins, circa 1905-1945; AM 2016-51; 1 folder (Folder 2)
  - Family and Group Photographs, circa 1875-1915; AM 2016-51; 1 folder (Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, circa 1915-1923; AM 2016-51; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Series 7: Clippings, undated; 1 box
  This series consists of various press clippings and entire periodicals that focus either on Rollins or the West.
  - Miscellaneous clippings (2 folders), dates not examined; portion of 1 box
  - Miscellaneous publications (1 folder), undated; portion of 1 box
- Series 8: Printed Material, undated; 1 box
  This series consists of pamphlets and assorted printed ephemera. Some make mention of Rollins or his work.
  - Pamphlets and ephemera, undated; 1 box
- Series 9: Souvenirs/Objects, undated; 1 box
  This series consists of an assortment of souvenirs acquired by Rollins. Among them include souvenirs from his Western travels as well as some souvenirs from his Princeton days.
  - Cloth sign from Yellowstone National Park, dates not examined; portion of 1 box
  - Sign bearing the Rollins names used on an ambulance during WWI and a small metal plate commemorating Princeton's involvement in the signing of the Declaration of Independence, dates not examined; portion of 1 box
  - Paper bag bearing Rollins's signature, dates not examined; portion of 1 box
  - leather lariat (EX 4517), dates not examined; portion of 1 box
  - 2 pairs of spurs (EX 4518), dates not examined; portion of 1 box
  - leather stirrup (broken) (EX 4519), dates not examined; portion of 1 box
  - horse shoe fragment (EX 4520), dates not examined; portion of 1 box
  - 2 bronze horse heads (EX 4522, 4523), signed on base "Gutzon Borglum" (creator of the presidential faces on Mt. Rushmore), undated; portion of 1 box
- 32101037676093 (Box 1)
- 32101037676085 (Box 2)
- 32101037676077 (Box 3)
- 32101037676069 (Box 4)
- 32101037676051 (Box 5)
- 32101036944641 (Box 19)
- 32101036944658 (Box 20)
- 32101036944674 (Box 21)
- 32101036944666 (Box 22)
- 32101037676044 (Box 6)
- 32101037676036 (Box 7)
- 32101037676028 (Box 8)
- 32101037676010 (Box 9)
- 32101080848185 (Box 25)
- 32101037676002 (Box 10)
- 32101037676317 (Box 11)
- 32101037676309 (Box 12)
- 32101037676291 (Box 13)
- 32101037676283 (Box 14)
- 32101037676275 (Box 15)
- 32101080599127 (Box B-000089)
- 32101037676267 (Box 16)
- 32101037676259 (Box 17)
- 32101037676242 (Box 18)